captures.com 2013-08-01

# Create a Web Page, Create a Free Web Page, Create Your Own Web Page

|   

Captures.com INC Consultants respects your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us on our Web sites. To that end, unless you designate otherwise or we state otherwise in this policy or at the time information is collected, any personal information you provide to Captures.com INC Consultants will be known only to two parties: you and Captures.com INC Consultants. The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our sites and their features. Personal information includes your name, street and e-mail addresses, billing information, click-through activity and any other personal information you may provide here.

Traffic data  
Each time a visitor comes to a Captures.com INC Consultants Web site, our servers -- like most on the Web -- collect some basic technical information, including, for example, the visitor's domain name (e.g., whether the user is logged on from aol.com or whitehouse.gov), referral data (e.g., we record the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking through to a Captures.com INC Consultants Web site) and browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform).

We also count, track the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our sites (e.g. tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the Captures.com INC Consultants sites, etc.). To these ends, we may merge information about visitors and visits into group data. 

Captures Newsletters   
In order to receive Captures Newsletters subscribers provide Captures with personal information including an e-mail address, and First Name. This information will not be sold or shared with anyone.

"E-mail to a friend" feature  
Captures.com INC Consultants offers an "e-mail a friend about this story" feature, allowing site visitors to send e-mail to friends to inform them about an article they might be interested in reading. In order for this feature to function, we ask for e-mail addresses for the recipient (so we know who to mail the message to) and from the sender (so we can tell the recipient who sent the e-mail). We do not store or save these addresses and you will not receive e-mail or other communications from Captures.com INC or its partners as a result of having used this feature.

"E-mail a friend about this story" is a mail service that individual visitors to Captures.com INC Consultants make use of to send individual e-mails. While this tool cannot be used to send mass "spam" mailings, Captures Consultants has no control over how our visitors use it, and any e-mail sent through it originates with, and is the responsibility of, the sender, not Captures.com INC Consultants. 

Other sites   
Captures.com INC Consultants contains many links to other sites on the Web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other Web sites.

Who can I ask if I have any additional questions?   
If you have any further questions or concerns about Captures.com INC privacy policies and use of personal information, please send them to [info@captures.com](mailto:info@captures.com)

|   
---|---
